

About Me

I myself is a dynamic person, responsible for work. I look forward to working in a energetic and professional environment to gain more experience and improve myself better.



0933531218



lephuctuongvy03@gmail.com



District 12, Ho Chi Minh City

EXPERTISE SKILL

- English: Intermediate
- Group Working Skill
- Computer: Word, Excel
- Self-study Skill
- Communication Skill
- Presentation Skill

LE PHUC TUONG VY

Apply for Intern Position

EDUCATION

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS

FPT University | 2021-Now Summer semester GPA: 8.82/10

EXPERIENCE

FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT AND FACEBOOK ADMIN

AO DAI - THEN AND NOW" PROJECT

08/06/2022 - 17/07/2022

Manage Fanpage on Facebook.

Attracted 1,801 hits and 1,564 interactions.

Content creator

Multimedia and Entertainment Club

12/2021 - 7/2022

Content writer and create idea for Christmas post of club and attracted 104 reactions.

Receive and send email to other clubs for media cooperation.

Media Staff

COLLABORATION - ECO CLUB Tran Dai Nghia High School for the Gifted

10/2019 - 03/2021

Write and upload posts via Facebook.

Introduce, consult products, workshop and answer comments via Facebook.

Find club information and contact media cooperation.

CERTIFICATES

COURSERA - Leading: Human Resource Management and Leadership

COURSERA - International Marketing & Cross Industry Growth

COURSERA - Human Resource Management: HR for People Managers